Finding Aid for D. James Galbraith Photographic Collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Oversize
  The Oversize series contains materials from both the Business Records and Private Photography series. These items retain the intellectual order of their originating series (Business Records or Private Photography), and can be found in both locations within the finding aid. The only exception is the Mostly Michigan Exhibit subseries, which consists of 16 x 20 framed pictures from an exhibit of Galbraith's work on display in Charlevoix, Michigan. Some of the images in this subseries are in color while others are in black and white.
  - Business Records
    - Exhibit Announcements and Programs undated (Box 11)
    - Portraits of Jim Galbraith undated (Box 11)
  - Private Photography
    - Commissions and Events
      - Ypsilanti Greek Theater 1963-1968 (Box 11)
      - Jack Chaffee undated (Box 11)
      - Robert Hamilton Scott undated (Box 11)
    - Life in Michigan
      - Miscellaneous undated (Box 11)
    - Mostly Michigan Exhibit
      - Foldenauer Farm, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 12)
      - Hartland Family Farm, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 12)
      - Yard Sale, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 12)
      - The Grovers, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 12)
      - Hartland Volunteer Fire Department, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 12)
      - Heritage, Hartland Township, MI 1983 (Box 12)
      - Shirley Halliday, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 12)
      - Elephant Man, South Lyon, MI 1972 (Box 13)
      - Shakey Jake Woods, Ann Arbor 1982 (Box 13)
      - Schizophrenia, Howell, MI 1970 (Box 13)
      - Charleszetta "Mother" Waddles Baptism, Hartland Township, MI 1973 (Box 13)
      - Family Art Parade 1973 (Box 13)
      - Didi, Howell, MI 1982 (Box 13)
      - Circus Tent Child, South Lyon, MI 1971 (Box 13)
      - Trafalgar Square, London, England 1970 (Box 13)
      - Michigan Farrier, Hartland Township, MI 1982 (Box 14)
      - Scheffler Family, Hartland Township, MI 1979 (Box 14)
      - Crawdad Hunter, Hartland Township, MI 1978 (Box 14)
      - Memorial Day Parade, Hartland Township, MI 1974 (Box 14)
      - Memorial Day Parade, Hartland Township, MI 1983 (Box 14)
      - Popeye (Joe Carey), Hartland Township, MI 1982 (Box 14)
      - Marion Hards, Hartland Township, MI 1983 (Box 14)
      - Friends, Frankfurt, MI 1979 (Box 14)
      - 5th Generation Circus Family, South Lyon, MI 1972 (Box 14)
      - February Shadows, Hartland Township, MI 1974 (Box 15)
      - Brutus & Kids, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 15)
      - Esther Lyons, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 15)
      - "King and Queen," Joe Tiano and Jennifer Tenaglia, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 15)
      - "Parshallville Vegetable Sale," Hartland Township, MI 1982 (Box 15)
      - "Fence Line," Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 15)
      - The Olde Mille Salon, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 15)
      - Mabel and Wilbur Steinacker, Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 15)
      - "Corporate Lunch," Howell, MI 1968 (Box 15)
      - "The Gandy Dancer," Brighton, MI 1973 (Box 16)
      - "Farm Worker," Fowlerville, MI 1979 (Box 16)
      - "Fenceline," Hartland Township, MI 1980 (Box 16)
      - Taquahmanon Falls, Paradise, MI 1970 (Box 16)
      - "NY Central," Ann Arbor, MI 1954 (Box 16)
      - "Listening," Livingston County Courthouse, Livingston County, MI 1980 (Box 16)
      - "Winter Sheep," Brighton, MI 1977 (Box 16)
      - "The Tice Family with Cindy," Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 16)
      - "Repent or Else," Hartland Township, MI 1985 (Box 16)
      - "Melon Parade," Howell, MI 1982 (Box 16)